

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018
 BACHELOR DEGREE IN
 SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
 GPA 3.03

Burapha University

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Typescript
- HTML
- Javascript
- CSS
- C#
- PHP
- SQL

FRAMEWORKS

- Angular
- ReactJS
- NodeJS
- ASP.NET
- NestJS

DATABASE

- SQL Server
- Mongo DB
- My SQL
- Oracle

PHROMPONG KHAGTES

[CHOPPER]

PROFILE

5 years experience in programmer. The scope of work includes Software development, Software structure design, Database management, Software testing for errors and debugging, Review the program regularly and make adjustments as necessary to ensure that it is functioning properly in accordance with current business and integrate new functions into existing applications.

EXPERIENCE

Sep 2023 - Present

Senior Full Stack Developer

Advanced Personnel and Solutions Co., Ltd. (Onsite TN Incorporation limited.)

Sales system: Government Savings Bank

- Develop back-end using NodeJS, RabbitMQ, MongoDB, SQL.
- Design API backend and Database Structure.
- · Agile Methodology.

Feb 2020 - Aug 2023

Full Stack Developer

Solution Link Co.Ltd. (Onsite PTT Digital Solutions Co.Ltd.)

NEW POS: PTT Oil and Retail Business PCL (OR)

- Develop back-end using NodeJS, RabbitMQ, Redis, .NET, MongoDB, SQL.
- Develop front-end using ReactJS.
- · Design database and workflow.
- Review a team member's source code before submitting to merge request.
- Create script for functional test (Mocha).

July 2019 - Jan 2020

Programmer

Fusion Solution Co.,Ltd.

<u>Cigna anywhere : Cigna Insurance PCL</u>

- Develop back-end using .NET.
- · Design database and workflow.



System Programmer

C.S.I. GROUP

Inventory management system: Panasonic Thailand

 Develop back-end and front-end using .NET, SQL , Store Procedure, Cystal Report, Javascript , HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.

Online request system: Yip In Tsoi Co., LTD.

 Develop back-end and front-end using .NET, SQL , Store Procedure, Cystal Report, Javascript , HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.

Product Line system: Teijin Polyester (Thailand) Limited.

 Develop back-end and front-end using .NET, SQL , Store Procedure, DevEpress Report, Javascript , HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.

OTHER

Schedule training management system: SEAC

• Develop back-end using .NET, MySQL

CCTV: AI FiRST

 Develop back-end and front-end using Angular, .NET, MySQL, Ashura, Yitu

Smart city on cloud: AI FiRST

• Develop back-end using NodeJS, MySQL, Clarify, Ashura

Electronic Right Offering: Asia wealth securities company limited

 Develop back-end and front-end using NodeJS, ReactJS, Mongo DB

Shipper System: Gulf Energy Development Public Company Limited

Develop back-end and front-end using NestJS, ReactJS, MySQL

